Seino! Galgal Channel GOGO!
Today I'd like to do a new project, a timeline of myself!
Looking forward to it!
This is a project to introduce myself, which was discussed at the planning meeting at the beginning of the year.
This is the start of the self-timeline project!
It's nice, isn't it?
Commemorative first installment!
I'm going to introduce myself this time.
I would like to invite three watchers to join us.
I look forward to working with you.
I've been with Misaki since her debut.
That's a long time.
I've heard a lot about your personal life.
I'm sure you've heard it all before.
I see.
Don't think I'm boring.
I'm thinking that you used to be a calligrapher.
But today, he hardly mentions anything since his debut.
On the contrary.
I'm going to talk about the period leading up to his debut.
I'm going to give you a lot of information.
I wonder if it's something you've never heard of.
like you've never heard of him before.
I'll walk you through it step by step.
Enjoy the show.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go.
Here you go.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm sure you are.
As a basic status.
Misaki Tsuruya.
That's my real name.
I use my real name.
I was born on April 18, 2003.
I was born on April 18, 2003, in the Year of the Sheep.
I'm a sheep. Sheep.
Sheep.
It's okay, it's okay.
Type B.
It's in my basic status.
I'm the only type B.
Oh, really?
That's right.
That's right, My Page.
I don't even have an AB.
We will be born in Fukuoka Prefecture in 2003!
Congratulations!
I was born in Fukuoka City, Fukuoka Prefecture.
I have parents and three older brothers.
Yes, sir.
And family.
Family.
Family
family
I was born in a general happy family.
That's nice.
Well, we've done some research, and she weighed about 2,900 grams, so...
I don't know.
That's good. It's okay.
just right
Just about right
About average
I was born about average
I was a very good child at that time.
I was so understanding from the time I was in the hospital.
Home was the other way around.
I guess that's when I was a genius.
So before we brought you home...
Yes.
Even Japanese people don't cry.
Oh, my God! Wow!
He seemed to be a very good boy.
He hasn't cried at night since he went home.
That's great!
Is he okay?
Yeah, he cries when he wants to eat.
She cries when she's tired.
Other than that, she doesn't cry.
Wow!
You're so good afterwards!
Super kids
Easy to raise
The mother said, "What an angel you've brought!
He's so understanding.
She's a good girl, and she's got it all together.
That's great!
But now that it's out there...
I'm basically a very curious person.
I'm insanely curious.
But at this time, I was still hiding it.
I kept it under wraps.
I see.
I don't get to see my dad that often because of his work.
My mom, who I'm usually with, thinks I'm a good kid. My mom, who I'm usually with, thinks I'm a nice girl.
But when I see my dad sometimes...
What is this guy?
He's hiding something.
I thought he was.
That's amazing.
I think he saw right through him.
So, he's been growing steadily since he was zero.
Fukuoka Prefecture. Still...
That's great. Not yet, not yet at all.
Around here, they start getting exposed to all kinds of things when they're about 4 years old.
We're going to nurture that curiosity.
The first thing I did was start piano and kumon when I was 4 years old.
That's early!
That's early.
Four years old.
That's right. I have almost no memory.
I have almost no memory.
Indeed.
Piano's going to be the longest lesson you've had.
I see.
Yes, well, that was quick.
Much earlier.
But I think that what I learned in those days is still very much alive.
You used to play the piano for me?
Yes, I played the piano and so on.
At the age of 6, I started calligraphy.
That's nice.
At this point, she's already a gifted writer.
Really?
You're a future U-boy.
He really is.
Your dad's out.
Yeah, he's in it a lot.
And then there's literature, right?
I'm a humanities major, but by the time I was 9, I was swimming and cherry-picking.
What happened?
Suddenly he became a sports fan. Suddenly I'm a sports guy.
Suddenly I was surprised
I've never heard of swimming before.
Well, it might have been my first time swimming, but, you know, I don't remember much about it.
How long have you been swimming?
Swimming, about two years.
But you're a good swimmer. You've been doing it for a long time.
Why don't you remember?
I don't.
No?
I don't swim 25 meters.
What's that?
I'm just curious. I've done a lot of things.
I'm the center of attention in the lessons.
I also played soccer for about three years.
And what changed at that time was that soccer players were very strict in their greetings.
Up to this point, I was a pretty good kid.
Yes, a lowly clown.
Yeah, but this is where they trained me.
I'm a pretty, you know, aggressive girl.
That's good.
Maybe it's a chance for me to become one.
Soccer, too.
Yeah.
I can now do what I did when I won MVP.
Wonderful.
Yes, well, that's about sixth grade, or is it fifth?
Or maybe grade 5.
Oh, pretty much.
When all the soccer girls in Fukuoka City got together.
Wonderful.
I said first place.
But, you know, I've been doing this for about two years.
But I can't really play soccer anymore.
What?
I can't really play, but I get MVP every week.
I'm learning how to... You know, what, learning lessons.
I cried every week.
It's so frustrating.
You can't?
Yeah, but he told me I couldn't.
That's what he said right away.
Because I'm just running around all the time.
What are you doing?
I can't do it.
Sometimes I use my hands and stuff.
I'd get a nose job on my stomach.
But it was so frustrating.
So from that time on, I was pretty competitive.
That's what I mean.
At the time you started swimming and playing soccer.
You mean you were taking 5 lessons at the same time?
Yes, that's right.
What?
So you were in lessons every day.
So you haven't stopped?
I haven't stopped.
I'm busy.
So it's all about once a week.
Almost every day.
Yeah, I was only doing lessons.
So basically, I didn't hang out with my friends.
Did you keep going to Kumomo after you started school?
Yes, I kept going.
That's great.
Now, I'm sure you're all wondering about the office aikatsu.
What is it?
When you turn 10, you start to mature a bit.
I've been thinking about it a little bit.
I'm a little embarrassed to say this, but...
I'm a little embarrassed to say this, but sometimes when I walk around Fukuoka...
"Would you like to join our office? Like, "Would you like to join our office?
That's nice.
You'll get more scouts. More scouts are coming.
I'm embarrassed to say this on YouTube, but...
I'm embarrassed to say this on YouTube, but I'm going to join a talent agency in Fukuoka.
I'm going to work for a talent agency in Fukuoka, where I'll do commercials and stuff like that.
You're in?
I did.
Your first bash.
Yeah, it's my first time.
How's the contract?
I've already left.
Did you quit?
Yes, that's why I'm with my second firm now.
What? You're a pro!
I'm the most professional.
But I didn't get any work here.
I just got in.
Like practice.
Yeah, you know, like weekly lessons, facial expressions, stuff like that.
That kind of thing.
Theater?
Theater.
I took theater lessons.
That's why I'm starting to like the entertainment business a little bit.
Yes, yes.
And then...
I came across an anime called Aikatsu.
Oh, Grandpa.
That's right.
And I thought, what a sparkling world.
Dancing? Singing? Idols? It was a bit new to me.
It was a new world for me.
I was really attracted to it.
So, I started a unit with the girl I was closest to at the time.
We're starting a unit.
What?
We call ourselves Double Star.
It's a win-win situation. This is a win-win situation.
He used to practice his gigs every day in the woods near our house.
I thought, "Wow, he's a great guy.
Yeah, and I'm thinking about taking a back seat.
That's awesome.
And he didn't even post it on his blog.
Isn't that great?
Since then, I've always wanted to be a part of a group.
You've been active in every activity.
Yeah.
And one year later, in 2010, at the age of 11.
I met E-Girls.
I see.
This is when I was watching the music station.
I think it was that year.
I saw them dance to "Sorry Kissing You".
I thought, "Who are these people?
There's this first Sayaka, right?
I thought, "What's this?
After that, every day when I came home from school, I would look at the music video.
I've become a real nerd.
That's amazing!
I really want to learn to dance in real life here.
I've already done so much.
Are you still doing it?
No, I'm not.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
He's doing a great job with the double stars.
I just wanted to read it on Wednesdays.
I quit when I was 10.
I'm about 13.
I can't tell my parents because I'm in too much trouble.
That's why I'm dancing.
There's this girl I was really close to... a double-star with a rough patch.
She's been dancing her whole life.
She's been doing it for a long time.
So I admired them a lot. That's why I admired them so much.
And I really wanted to do dance as my sole passion.
I'm going to be 12 years old now.
For the past year, I haven't been able to say that I like dancing.
I would imitate Ygaluz in the mirror in my room.
When my parents come in...
Why aren't you doing it?
I was too embarrassed to tell them.
There was a period of about a year or two
I had a period of about a year or two.
And finally, when I turned 12.
I couldn't take it anymore.
I want to start dancing.
I'm crying in the parking lot of the mall
to my mother
I want to dance, I want to dance.
And there I was.
And I really wanted to join EXPG.
But she said it's impossible because the level is too high.
So I said, "Let's start dancing at a local school.
I finally started dancing when I was 12 years old.
That's how I started dancing.
And in the summer of that year
I was going to perform at a summer festival.
It was like a festival for local studios.
You danced Ygaluz's "Anniversary" at the festival.
That's right.
Anniversary.
And then my father saw the video.
He finally came out.
You're right.
It's the first time since he was zero years old.
He said...
Can't you get in an apeice?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
He told me.
So I'll finally get into PG in the fall when I'm 12. So I finally got into PG in the fall when I was 12 years old.
From then on, all I could think about was PG.
I even started going to school in the afternoon.
I was that absorbed in it at that time.
Even though it was only once a week.
That's right.
I see.
But I was working so hard, and feeling so frustrated...
I worked really hard.
At the age of 14, I became a special student at EXP Kotobuki Fukuoka School.
It's not that common to go from a regular student to a high school student.
It's not so common to come from an ordinary student to a high school student.
But by some chance, I became a high school student at the age of 14, and I became a special student.
At that time, I quit all my lessons.
Oh, I'm done.
You're a special student?
That's right.
It was then and there that I realized that this is what I've always wanted.
I've always wanted to quit.
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to quit.
I always wanted to quit.
Yeah, I wanted to quit for a long time, and now I finally have one.
Oh, my God.
I got the one I've always wanted.
That's great.
But I haven't been dancing very long, so I don't really understand the culture of dance, the clothes, the hair...
Clothing is difficult, isn't it?
That's why I was having a hard time fitting in.
I was really insecure, really insecure.
So in the summer when I was 14 years old, there was an audition and I asked if I could come and take it.
I asked her if she wanted to audition for Maho player Majima Jo Pure's.
I couldn't really dance hip-hop at all, so I thought I might be able to shine.
I thought I might be able to shine because I couldn't dance hip-hop at all, and at that time I was doing Miracle Tune.
I was doing Miracle Tune at the time, so I thought I might be able to do well in that area.
I'm coming to Tokyo. I'm coming to Tokyo.
I'm lost at the Shiodome meeting.
It's difficult, isn't it?
I'm sorry you had to make a choice so suddenly.
And the day before the audition, I'm staying at a hotel next to the audition site.
When I got there, it was like the hotel had made reservations at another one of their restaurants.
I'm here with my mom, but we're going to Tokyo, so we're going to stay here.
I had to get a hotel there on short notice.
We got it back.
That's great.
You know...
It was really hard work at that time.
But by the time we got to Fukuoka School, Kira and I were...
I met her there.
We met, and then we cleared the audition 2:00 and 3:00, and then we made our debut as Magical Magical.
I made my debut as Magical Magical.
That's wonderful!
Yes.
But then I moved to Tokyo, and I'm still working as Girls Girls.
So close
I'm already on the market.
Was that too long?
No, it's fine.
It's gonna be okay.
I read one more book.
I'm very happy with that.
It's an interesting life, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's like you've become who you're meant to be.
You're a great actor.
You're a super kid now.
That's true.
That's why you were so stoic from then on.
Don't cry.
To myself.
Not now. Not now.
That's great.
I wasn't crying.
I didn't think it would be this long.
It's like a double star.
It sure is.
Wow.
A video?
Definitely.
Footage.
The first video.
What should we do with Yuichan?
Yui-cchan!
Yui-can
Yui-cchan
I like Yui-chan.
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yes, I like her.
Excellent!
So that's my review, thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was a lot of fun.
I hope you all enjoyed it and I hope you all enjoyed it.
If you like this video, please subscribe to the channel and leave a comment and a good button!
Bye bye!
Bye bye bye.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Mmm.
Mmm
Mm-hmm.